<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SHCDs on Cray Site Init</title><link>https://cray-hpe.github.io/cray-site-init/shcds/</link><description>Recent content in SHCDs on Cray Site Init</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://cray-hpe.github.io/cray-site-init/shcds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Running integration tests with canu and csi</title><link>https://cray-hpe.github.io/cray-site-init/shcds/running_integration_tests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cray-hpe.github.io/cray-site-init/shcds/running_integration_tests/</guid><description>The SHCD is the beginning source-of-truth for how a system is laid out and connected. The information found there is used through several different tools throughout the install of CSM, so if changes are made to an SHCD, it can be beneficial in both development and production environments to see how those changes might propagate.
To that end, there are some integration tests built in to csi that can test the flow mentioned above, which allow you to generate seed files for multiple systems at once.</description></item><item><title>Using a canu-generated shcd.json with csi</title><link>https://cray-hpe.github.io/cray-site-init/shcds/using_shcds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cray-hpe.github.io/cray-site-init/shcds/using_shcds/</guid><description>In CSM 1.2+ csi will have the ability to ingest a JSON file and automatically generate the seed files needed for the csi config init command.
Seed Files csi config init relies on several &amp;ldquo;seed&amp;rdquo; files in oder to produce a Shasta configuration payload:
hmn_connections.json: maps which switch ports on the Leaf switches are cabled to what the River node BMCs, PDUs, or other hardware ncn_metadata.csv: maps the MACs of the Management NCNs to their xnames and is used to initialize the management cluster switch_metadata.</description></item></channel></rss>